Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
  - Area L - Western, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    - Devon, Totnes, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/504; 1.0 file
    - Bath, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/505; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Bridgwater, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/506; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/507; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Taunton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/508/1; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Taunton, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/508/2; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Taunton, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/508/3; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Wells, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/509; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Weston-super-Mare, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/510; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Yeovil, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/511; 1.0 file
  - Area M - Wales and Monmouthshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/512-CCO 1/11/547
    - Anglesey, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/512; 1.0 file
    - Brecon and Radnor, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/513; 1.0 file
    - Caernarvon, Caernarvon, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/514; 1.0 file
    - Caernarvon, Conway, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/515; 1.0 file
    - Cardigan, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/516; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/517; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, Llanelly, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/518; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/519; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/520/1; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/520/2; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/520/3; 1.0 file
    - Flint East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/521; 1.0 file
    - Flint West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/522; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/523; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/524; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff South East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/525; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/526; 1.0 file
    - Merthyr Tydfil, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/527; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/528; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/529; 1.0 file
    - Swansea East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/530; 1.0 file
    - Swansea West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/531; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Aberavon, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/532; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Barry, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/533; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Caerphilly, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/534; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Gower, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/535; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Neath, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/536; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Ogmore, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/537; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Pontypridd, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/538; 1.0 file
    - Merioneth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/539; 1.0 file
    - Newport, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/540/1; 1.0 file
    - Newport, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/540/2; 1.0 file
    - Newport, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/540/3; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Abertillery, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/541; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Bedwellty, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/542; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Ebbw Vale, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/543; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Monmouth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/544; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/545; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/546; 1.0 file
    - Pembroke, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/547; 1.0 file
  - Area N - Scotland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/548-CCO 1/11/618
    - Aberdeen North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/548; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeen South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/549; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/550; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/551; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, Dundee, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/552/553; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, Dundee East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/552; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, Dundee West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/553; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, North Angus and Mearns, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/554; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, Angus South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/555; 1.0 file
    - Argyll, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/556; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Ayr, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/557; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Bute and North Ayrshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/558; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Central Ayrshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/559; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Kilmarnock, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/560; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, South Ayrshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/561; 1.0 file
    - Banffshire, Banff, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/562; 1.0 file
    - Berwick and East Lothian, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/563; 1.0 file
    - Caithness and Sutherland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/564; 1.0 file
    - Dumfries, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/565; 1.0 file
    - Dumbartonshire East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/566; 1.0 file
    - Dumbartonshire West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/567; 1.0 file
    - Fife, Dunfermline Burghs, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/568; 1.0 file
    - Fife, Kirkaldy Burghs, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/569; 1.0 file
    - Fife, East Fife, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/570; 1.0 file
    - Fife, West Fife, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/571; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Inverness, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/572; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Ross and Cromarty, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/573; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Western Isles, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/574; 1.0 file
    - Kircudbrightshrie and Wigtownshire, Galloway, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/575; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Bridgeton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/576; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Cathcart, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/577; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Central, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/578; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Craigton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/579; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Gorbels, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/580; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Govan, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/581; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Hillhead, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/582; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Kelvingrove, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/583; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Maryhill, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/584; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Pollock, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/585; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Provan, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/586; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Scotstoun, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/587; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Shettleston, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/588; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Springburn, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/589; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Woodside, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/590; 1.0 file
    - Coatbridge and Airdrie, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/591; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Bothwell, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/592; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Hamilton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/593; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Lanark, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/594; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Motherwell, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/595; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/596; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Rutherglen, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/597; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Central, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/598; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/599; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh, Leith, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/600; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh, North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/601; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh, Pentlands, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/602; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/603; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/604; 1.0 file
    - Midlothian, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/605; 1.0 file
    - Roxburgh, Selkirk and Peebles, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/606; 1.0 file
    - Moray and Nairnshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/607; 1.0 file
    - Orkney and Zetland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/608; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Kinross and West Perthshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/609; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Perth and East Perthshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/610; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Greenock, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/611/1; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Greenock, By-Election, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/611/2; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, Paisley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/612; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, East Renfrewshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/613; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, West Renfrewshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/614; 1.0 file
    - Stirling and Falkirk Burghs, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/615; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, Clackmannan and East Stirlingshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/616; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, West Stirlingshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/617; 1.0 file
    - West Lothian, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/618; 1.0 file
  - Area O - Northern Ireland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/619-CCO 1/11/630
    - Northern Ireland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/619/630; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Mar 1955-Feb 1957; [CCO 1/11/619]
    - Mid-Ulster By-Election, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/620; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
  - Area A - London, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/1-CCO 1/12/42
    - Baron's Court, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/1; 1.0 file
    - Battersea North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/2; 1.0 file
    - Battersea South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/3; 1.0 file
    - Bermondsey, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/4; 1.0 file
    - Bethnal Green, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/5; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/6; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/7; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/8; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/9/1; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/9/2; 1.0 file
    - Abbey, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/9/3; 1.0 file
    - St. George's, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/9/4; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/10; 1.0 file
    - Fulham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/11; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/12; 1.0 file
    - Hackney Central, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/13; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/14; 1.0 file
    - Hampstead, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/15; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/16; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/17; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/18/1; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, By-Election (file A), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/18/2; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/18/3; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/19; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/20; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/21; 1.0 file
    - Brixton (Lambeth), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/22; 1.0 file
    - Norwood (Lambeth), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/23; 1.0 file
    - Vauxhall (Lambeth), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/24; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/25/1; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, By-Election (file A), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/25/2; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/25/3; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/26; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/27; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/28; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/29; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/30; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/31; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/32; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/33/1; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, By-Election (file A), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/33/2; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/33/3; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/34; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/35; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/36; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/37; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Clapham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/38; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Putney, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/39; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Streatham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/40; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/41; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/42; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/43-CCO 1/12/76
    - Carlisle, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/43; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Penrith and the Border, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/44; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/45; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/46; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/47; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/48/49; 1.0 file
    - Jarrow, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/50; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/51; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/52; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/53/54; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/53; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/54; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/55; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Auckland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/56/1; 1.0 file
    - Durham County Group, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/56/2; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/57; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/58; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/59; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/60; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/61; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/62; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West Durham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/63; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/64; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/65; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/66; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/67; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/68/1; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, By-Election (file A), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/68/2; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/69; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/70; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/71; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/72; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/73; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/74; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/75/76; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/75; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/76; 1.0 file
  - Area C - North West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/77-CCO 1/12/155
    - Altrincham and Sale, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/77; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/78; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/79; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/80/81; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/80; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/81; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/82; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/83; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/84; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/85; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/86; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/87; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Nantwich, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/88; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/89; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/90; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/91; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/92; 1.0 file
    - Central Lancashire Group, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/93/1; 1.0 file
    - Accrington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/93/2; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-under-Lyne, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/94; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in-Furness, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/95; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/96; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/97/98; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/98; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/99/100; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/99; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/100; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/101; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/102; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/103; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/104; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/105; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/106; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/107/115; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Edgehill, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/107; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Exchange, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/108; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Garston, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/109/1; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Garston, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/109/2; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Kirkdale, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/110; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Scotland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/111; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Toxteth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/112; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Walton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/113; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Wavertree, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/114; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, West Derby, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/115; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/116/124; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Ardwick, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/116; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Blackley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/117; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Cheetham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/118; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Exchange, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/119; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Gorton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/120; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/121; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Openshaw, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/122; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Withington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/123; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Wythenshawe, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/124; 1.0 file
    - Nelson and Colne, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/125; 1.0 file
    - Oldham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/126/127; 1.0 file
    - Oldham East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/126; 1.0 file
    - Oldham West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/127; 1.0 file
    - Preston, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/128/129; 1.0 file
    - Preston North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/128; 1.0 file
    - Preston South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/129; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/130/1; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/130/2; 1.0 file
    - Rossendale, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/131; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/132/1; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/132/2; 1.0 file
    - Salford, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/133/134; 1.0 file
    - Salford East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/133; 1.0 file
    - Salford West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/134; 1.0 file
    - [Southport], [Mar 1957-Feb 1959]; [CCO 1/12/135]
      [Vacant]
    - Stretford, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/136; 1.0 file
    - Warrington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/137; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/138/1; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/138/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Chorley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/139; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Clithero, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/140; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Darwen, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/141; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/142; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/143; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Huyton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/144; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ince, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/145; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Lancaster, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/146; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Middleton and Prestwich, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/147; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/148/1; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/148/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Newton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/149; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, North Fylde, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/150; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/151; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, South Fylde, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/152; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/153; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Widnes, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/154; 1.0 file
    - Westmorland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/155/1; 1.0 file
    - Combined English Universitites, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/155/2; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/156-CCO 1/12/209
    - Barnsley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/156; 1.0 file
    - Batley and Morley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/157; 1.0 file
    - Bradford, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/158/161; 1.0 file
    - Bradford East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/158; 1.0 file
    - Bradford North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/159; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/160; 1.0 file
    - Bradford West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/161; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/162; 1.0 file
    - Dewsbury, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/163; 1.0 file
    - Doncaster, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/164; 1.0 file
    - Halifax, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/165; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/166/167; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/166; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/167; 1.0 file
    - Keighley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/168; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/169/171; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/169; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/170; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/171; 1.0 file
    - Leeds, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/172/177; 1.0 file
    - Leeds East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/172; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/173; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/174; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/175; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/176; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/177; 1.0 file
    - Pontefract, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/178; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/179; 1.0 file
    - Rotherham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/180; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/181/186; 1.0 file